Finding Aid for the Robert A. McGaw Map Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Map of the Cherokee Nation Indian Territory, 1900; 112; ID: 112 Map #: B Map Title: Map of the Cherokee Nation Indian Territory Date of Creation: 1900 Cartographer: R.L. McAlpine Engraver: Julius Bien and Co. Place of Publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: U.S. Department of the Interior Source of Information: "Eighth Annual Report, Commission to the Five Civilized Tribes" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 35x25.75 Notes: Territory shown is in Oklahoma. Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer